export const airportminimums = [
  { front: "CAT I", back: "HAT - 200' RVR - 2400' or 1800 w/ Center Line Lights and Touchdown Zone Lines" },
  { front: "CAT II (SA)", back: "HAT - 150'<br>RVR - 1400'" },
  { front: "CAT II", back: "HAT - 100'<br>RVR - 1200'" },
  { front: "CAT IIIA", back: "HAT - 100'<br>RVR - 700'" },
  { front: "CAT IIIB", back: "HAT - 50'<br>RVR - 150'" },
  { front: "CAT IIIC", back: "HAT - 0'<br>RVR - 0'<br>(Not Authorized in USA)" },
  { front: "Origin<br>Standard Takeoff Minimums", back: "With 2 Engines Operative - 1SM<br>With 3+ Engines Operative - 1/2SM<br>(FAR 121.617)" },
  { front: "What do we use for Standard Takeoff Minimums?", back: "C-078 or JEPP-9A" },
  { front: "Standard Alternate Minimums<br>Not in our Ops Spec", back: "Precision - 600'-2SM<br>Non-Precision - 800'-2SM" },
  { front: "C-055 Alternate Minimums", back: "1 Approach - +400'-1SM<br>2 Approach - +200'-1/2SM(To the highest)" },
  { front: "When is a Departure Alternate Required?", back: "When weather is below landing minimums at the departure airport" },
  { front: "How Far Can a Departure Alternate be for a 2 Engine Aircraft?", back: "1 Hour, In Still Air, With 1 Engine Inoperative" },
  { front: "How Far Can a Departure Alternate be for a 3+ Engine Aircraft?", back: "2 Hours, In Still Air, With 1 Engine Inoperative" },
	{ front : "How far can a departure alternate for a 2 engine aircraft?", back: "2 Engine: 1 hour, in still air, with 1 engine inoperative" },
	{ front : "How far can a departure alternate for a 3+ engine aircraft?", back: "3+ Engine: 2 hour, in still air, with 1 engine inoperative" },
	{ front : "When is a departure alternate required?", back: "When weather is below landing minimums at the departure (FAR 121.617)" },
	{ front : "What are C-055 alternate minimums?", back: "1 Approach: +400' + 1SM<br>2 Approach: +200' +1/2SM" },
	{ front : "What are standard alternate minimums?", back: "Precision: 600-2<br>Non-Precision: 800-2" },
	{ front : "What are standard takeoff minimums?", back: "2 Engine: 1SM<br>3+ Engine: 1/2SM" },
	{ front : "When is a drift down alternate required?", back: "When you cannot maintain method 1" },
	{ front : "When is a destination alternate required?", back: "It's required when + or - 1 hour the ETA, the TAF indicates less than... 2000' ceiling &/or 3SM of visibility<br>(FAR 121.619)" },
	{ front : "When is a second alternate required?", back: "When weather for the destination and first alternate are marginal<br>Marginal = 600-2" },
	{ front : "What is a High Minimum Captain?", back: "A captain with less than 100 hours in aircraft type" },
	{ front : "What minimums are affected by a High Minimum Captain?", back: "the Landing minimums" },
	{ front : "What is a Restricted Captain?", back: "CAT II Qualified, but not current" },
	{ front : "What must a Restricted Captain do to maintain currency?", back: "Must have 3 CAT II approaches every 6 months" },
	{ front : "What defines 2 different approaches?", back: "2 different runways (R9 & R27)<br>2 different NAVAID ID's (IABC + IDEF)" },
	{ front : "Using C-055, with 1 NAVAID, what do you do to the following?<br>HAT - 200'<br>Visibility - 1/2SM", back: "HAT - 600'<br>Visibility - 1 1/2SM" },
	{ front : "Using C-055, with 1 NAVAID, what do you do to the following?<br>HAT - 250'<br>Visibility - 1/2SM", back: "HAT - 700'<br>Visibility - 1 1/2SM" },
	{ front : "Using C-055, with 2 NAVAIDs, what do you do to the following?<br>HAT - 200' Visibility - 1/2SM<br>HAT - 250' Visibility - 3/4SM", back: "HAT - 500'<br>Visibility - 1 1/4SM" },
	{ front : "Using C-055, with 2 NAVAIDs, what do you do to the following?<br>HAT - 200' Visibility - 1/2SM<br>HAT - 200' Visibility - 1/2SM", back: "HAT - 300'<br>Visibility - 1SM" },
	{ front : "Using C-055, with 2 NAVAIDs, what do you do to the following?<br>HAT - 225' Visibility - 1/2SM<br>HAT - 200' Visibility - 3/4SM", back: "HAT - 500'<br>Visibility - 1 1/4SM" },
	{ front : "How do you apply C-055 alternate minimums 2 NAVAID rule?", back: "To the highest of the two chosen plate minimums" },
	{ front : "What do you for a High Minimum Captain at the departure airport?", back: "Add 100' HAT and + 1/2SM (always RVR)" },
	{ front : "What do you for a High Minimum Captain at the destination airport?", back: "Add 100' HAT and + 1/2SM (always RVR)" },
	{ front : "What do you for a High Minimum Captain at an alternate airport?", back: "No less than 300' HAT and + 1SM (always RVR)" },
	{ front : "What do we use for standard takeoff minimums?", back: "C-078 / JEPP-9A" },
];
